本字幕由天满宫字幕组制作，翻译:neko，字幕:neko 校对:中校:neko，英校cinewamage，请在下载后24小时内删除，若因私自传播造成的法律责任，字幕君概不负责。
What's it?
这是什么？
This is gonna hurt like a bitch, boy
这会像个婊子一样疼，小子
Thank you sir.
谢谢您，主♂人。
AHHH!AHHHH!
啊啊~啊啊啊！
Thank you sir!
谢谢您，主♂人！
Yeah.
Come on. Yeah, that's it. Line it up.
走吧。对，就是这样。排成一线。
Get your ass back there, boy.
回到那边去，小子。
Come on, straight line.
走，排成一条直线。
Get your ass back. That's it. Yeah.
回去。就是这样。
Stand up. Come on. This way. Good fucking boy.
站起来。走。真特么是个好男孩。
That's it. Take the chains off, boys.
就是这样。把链子解开，男孩们。
Chest out. Spread those legs. Good boy.
挺胸。张开双腿。好男孩。
Did you jack off in the cell last night boy? No, sir. You are fucking lie to me! I swear I didn't jack off last night, sir. I came in my sleep.
你昨晚在牢房里打飞机了吗，小子？没有，主人。你他妈的在对我说谎！我发誓昨晚没打，主人。我是在睡梦中射精的。
Alpha Slave Titus?
阿尔法奴隶提图斯？
Yes sir.
是的，主人。
Make sure you strap him up at night so this won't happen again.
确保晚上给他系好带子，这样就不会再发生这种事情了。
Yes sir.
是，主人。
Where's puppy boy?
那个狗男孩在哪里？
I don't know sir.
我不知道，主人。
What the fuck do you mean you don't know?
你他妈的是什么意思，你不知道？
You let him run away again, didn't you?
你又让他逃走了，对吗？
No sir.
不知道，主人。
Yeah?
哈啊？
Look at you.
看看你。
Fucking slacking off for the past week.
这一周一直在混日子。
You're getting soft.
你变得软弱了。
Fuck.
操。
The hell I am.
我生气了。
We've had enough of you, man.
我们受够你了，伙计。
Come on.
来吧。
What the fuck?
卧槽？
Come on, let's take a turn.
来吧，让我们轮流来揍你。
Come on.
来吧。
Ah!
啊！
Fuck!
草！
shit!
妈的！
Come on!
来！
Ah!
啊！
You're not my master.
你不再是我的主人了。
You like?
你喜欢这样吗？
Ah!
啊！
Oh, fuck!
哦，操！
Fuck!
草！
Son of a bitch!
混蛋！
You like?
你喜欢这样吗？
Come on!
来！
Agh!
Oh, yeah!
Son of a bitch!
他娘的！
Aah!
Shit!
妈的！
Yeah, fuck!
You like?
你喜欢这样吗？
Aah!
Fuck!
草！
Let's get the hell out of here.
我们赶紧离开这里。
It's all yours, boys.
我都听你的，男孩们。
Ah, shit!
啊，该死！
Alright, let's blow a load on him and get out of here.
好的，让我们对他打一发♂然后离开这里。
Fuck!
操！
Fuck you!
操你妈的！